接口在真正的Java代码中被广泛使用。
Interfaces are used pervasively in real Java code.
不是每个类都与接口关联，
Not every class is associated with interface,
但有几个很好的理由
but there are a few good reasons to bring
代码的接口。
an interface into your code.
首先，它们是很好的文档
First, they are good documentation
对于编译器和人类来说。
for both the compiler and for humans.
接口不仅帮助编译器
Not only does the interface help the compiler
捕获ADT实现错误，如忘记
catch ADT implementation bugs like forgetting
为了实现一个特定的操作，
to implement a particular operation,
但对人类来说也更有用
but it's also much more useful for a human
读取比代码更具体的实现
to read than the code for a concrete implementation
因为实现散布ADT级别的类型
because an implementation intersperses ADT level types
以及带有实现细节的规范。
and specs with implementation details.
而接口没有。
And interface does not.
允许性能权衡是另一个原因
Allowing performance trade-offs is another reason
用于使用接口。
for using interfaces.
ADT的不同实现
Different implementations of the ADT
可以提供具有非常不同性能的方法
can provide methods with very different performance
特点。
characteristics.
不同的应用程序可能在不同的选择下工作得更好
Different apps may work better with different choices
在这些实现中。
of those implementations.
但我们还是希望用一种
But we'd still like to code those apps in a way that
代表独立。
is representation independent.
所以从正确的角度来看，
So from a correctness standpoint,
应该可以直接掉下去
it should be possible to just drop
在任何一个重要ADT的新实现中
in any new implementation of an important ADT
最多只需要简单的本地化代码更改。
with simple, localized code changes at best.
我们可以对接口使用可选方法。
We can use optional methods with interfaces.
Java标准库中的So列表
So list from the Java standard library
将所有mutator方法标记为可选。
marks all mutator methods as optional.
通过构建一个
By building an implementation that
不支持这些方法，我们可以提供不可变列表。
does not support these methods, we can provide immutable lists.
有些操作很难实施
Some operations are hard to implement
在不可变列表上有足够好的性能，
with good enough performance on immutable lists,
所以我们也需要可变的实现。
so we want mutable implementations as well.
不调用变异器的代码可以
Code that doesn't call mutators can
被编写成自动处理任何一种列表。
be written to work automatically with either kind of list.
方法与故意低于规定的规格
Methods with intentionally under determined specifications
可能有用。
can be useful.
例如，有限集的ADT
For example, an ADT for finite sets
无法指定元素顺序
could leave unspecified the element order
当你把集合转换成一个列表时得到的。
that you get back when you convert the set into a list.
实际上，Java集合的
In fact, the Java collection's set
就是这样定义的。
is precisely defined in that way.
有些实现可能使用较慢的方法实现
Some implementations might use a slower method implementation
设法保持集合表示的
that manages to keep the set representation
以某种排序顺序允许快速转换
in some sorted order allowing quick conversion
排序列表。
to a sorted list.
但其他实现可能会进行许多其他操作
But other implementations might make many other operations
不必费心支持转换，速度更快
faster by not bothering to support conversion
排序列表。
to sorted lists.
所以这就交给了实现者。
So that leaves it up to the implementer.
它还允许一个类的多个视图。
It also allows multiple views of one class.
因此一个Java类可以实现多个方法。
So a Java class may implement multiple methods.
例如，用户界面小部件
For example, a user interface widget
程序员可以查看显示下拉列表
displaying a drop-down list could be viewed by a programmer
作为一个小部件，作为一个用户界面，作为一个列表。
both as a widget, as a user interface thing, and as a list.
这个小部件的类可以实现这两个接口。
The class for this widget could implement both interfaces.
换句话说，我们不需要多次实现ADT
In other words, we don't need to implement an ADT multiple times
只是因为我们选择了不同的数据结构。
just because we're choosing different data structures.
我们可以做多种实现
We might make multiple implementations
因为有很多不同种类的物体
because many different kinds of objects
可视为ADT的特例
can be seen as special cases of the ADT
以及其他有用的观点。
along with other useful perspectives.
接口也让我们拥有越来越少的
Interfaces also allow us to have more and less
值得信赖的实现。
trustworthy implementations.
这是实施--
This is a good reason for implementing--
实现的调试原因
a debugging reason for implementing
一个接口多次。
an interface multiple times.
所以很容易，通常很容易，构建简单的实现
So it's easy, typically easy, to build simple implementation
你能说服自己是正确的。
that you can convince yourself is correct.
一旦你做到了，你可以更加努力地工作
And once you've done that, you can work harder
创造一个更华丽的版本。
to build a fancier version.
但这将更有可能包含bug。
But that will be more likely to contain bugs.
然后您可以选择实现
And then you can choose the implementation
根据应用程序有多糟来使用
to use for your application based on how bad it would
被虫子咬了。
be to get bitten by a bug.
您还可以使用这些多个实现
And you can also use these multiple implementations
当你试着调试时把它们调进调出。
for swapping them in and out when you're trying to debug.
最后，我们可以扩展ADT概念的Java工具箱，
So finally, we can extend our Java toolbox of ADT concepts,
以及如何在Java中实现这些概念
of concepts and how they're implemented in Java, that we
在第一个ADT读数中看到。
saw in the first ADT reading.
对于抽象数据类型，我们可以表示它
For an abstract data type, we can represent it either
作为一个类——string就是一个例子--
as a single class-- and string is an example of that--
或者我们可以将其表示为与类的接口
or we can represent it as an interface with class
实现。
implementations.
列表，带有数组列表或链表，
And list, with array list or linked list,
就是一个例子。
is an example of that.
对于creator操作，我们可以使用构造函数
For creator operations, we can use a constructor
就像数组列表构造函数一样。
like the array list constructor.
我们可以使用静态方法，也称为工厂方法，
We can use a static method, also called a factory method,
要列出的数组和单例列表就是这样的例子。
Arrays to list and singleton list are examples of that.
我们之前看到的神秘感的价值
So is value of in the myString that we saw earlier
在这篇文章里。
in this reading.
或者我们可以在大整数ADT中使用像0这样的常量。
Or we can use a constant value like 0 in the big integer ADT.
对于观察者操作，它们可能是实例方法
For observer operations, they might be instance methods
就像在名单上一样。
like get on a list.
它们可能是静态方法，如集合中的max
They might be static methods like max in the collections
上课。
class.
对于生产者来说，它们又可以是实例方法
For producers, they can again be instance methods
或静态方法。
or static methods.
同样地，突变子也可以
And likewise, mutators can either
是实例方法还是静态方法。
be instance methods or static methods.
和以前一样，
And the representation, as before,
是类中的私有字段。
is the private fields inside a class.